= kisskh.lv =
I saw you in Belle's posts.
I even thought you were her boyfriend.
Huh?
He's just my friend!
I still want to get to know
Belle and study her better.
Study her?
"Study her," huh?
What do you think
she is, a science project?
Honestly, I'm worried...
because we all know
that Lorenz is her trigger.
Just always listen to this.
No matter how complicated
Belle may be…
I’m sure her true feelings
for you will always come through.
But it’s still different when you
have someone to share your life with.
Someone who also has direction.
Belle...
I’d like to feature you on
our magazine show.
Okay, I'll do it.
My name is...Ysabelle Navarro.
I have a mental disorder.
It's called Dissociative
Identity Disorder.
He's just using you!
Estong, I'm the one
who's using you.
Actually, both of you.
You.
Did you think I forgot
what you did to me on our first date?
How you were ashamed of me?
How you were scared of me?
How much you were disgusted by me?
And how you just left me on our first date?
Well, no.
I haven't forgotten about it.
I'll never forget it,
and now...
do you think you can fool me again?
Do you think I didn't intentionally
reach out to you first?
I want to make it up to her.
Oh, there you go.
What did you think, Lorenz?
That you're fooling me again?
The past
isn't meant to be forgotten.
It's supposed to be answered for.
Do I really need to sign that?
Isn’t it enough that I agreed?
Just wait until your
show is over, Lorenz...
You'll wish
you had never come back to me.
I want to prove to you...
that I can humiliate you
and make you hope for nothing.
And now...
say goodbye to a good story,
because I won't allow you to air
the footage we shot anymore.
No.
You can't do that.
You agreed to do this,
right?
How?
Verbally?
You can't use that against me.
But me...
I have something to use against you.
What you did was also
kind of embarrassing, right?
Because no matter how we look at it…
you’re still not in your right mind.
Oh, so you’re a prick, huh?
You’ve been at it this whole time.
- What, you wanna fight?
- I'm going to show everyone...
everything you've done to me.
Your unethical behavior
as a media producer...
and what you and
your Senior Story Producer
slash girlfriend, did to me.
Oh, right. I also knew that.
I'll make sure...
that both of you will get cancelled,
and I'll make sure
you can never work
for a media company
ever again.
Belle.
Surely by now...
you've already realized
that I only used you
so I could get back with Lorenz.
This is on you.
You wouldn't leave me alone,
you were so stubborn.
So, Estong...
stay away from me.
Leave me alone.
Okay?
Because you can't help me.
You can't even help yourself,
so how could you even help me?
You don't need to worry about me
because I can handle myself.
I can control all of them now.
I don't need your help.
What happened?
Uh...sweetheart?
Sweetie. Drink your medicine.
Go on.
You asked me before what this was.
Everything that happened while
you were gone is in here.
What is that for?
I don't need that.
I don't need to know more.
It's not really just about your
personalities, sweetheart.
I already told you everything.
But all of the details about
what happened between
you and Estong are here.
You know, sweetheart,
Estong is a good person.
So what you did to him was very wrong.
It was wrong to use him just
to get revenge on Lorenz.
He was always there for you,
despite not fully knowing you at first.
He protected you so many times.
All Estong ever did was be true to you.
He knows about your condition.
He knows everything.
But he never left,
even though he had every reason to.
That's why I empathize for Estong.
I feel bad for him because
he's a good person.
He just wanted you to be safe.
But fine, if you don't
want to apologize to him...
we won't force you.
But I just hope...
you'll be fair.
Ysa is my friend.
A close friend.
And so are your other personalities.
Kuya Estong, are we friends now?
Oh, sure!
Friends!
You bring out the best of us.
...getting too—
Don't, don't, don't—
Hey!
...Ysa's—
Okay—
...for helping us—
So I hope
I can be friends with you too, Belle.
Uh...can I try the...
grilled chicken salad,
margherita pizza, chicken barbecue pizza...
uh, fried chicken...
uh, two extra rice, please.
Uh, and one...
Ysabelle's Mocha Magic.
Uh, make it large and zero sugar.
I'm on a calorie deficit.
Uh, I'll also have a donut.
Uh, okay.
But we don't have fried chicken and rice.
We're a café.
Oh, okay. I'll just have
the croissant instead.
- Oh, okay, okay.
- She said croissant, bro
- Okay, croi—
- Estong?
Hello.
Bro, you got it from here, okay?
Hey, hey, Kuya, Kuya...
Wait, wait.
I need to go number two.
- You do it.
- You just went number two earlier.
- No, no, Kuya...
- You can handle this.
I still want to. I still want to, okay?
This might turn into a
three or four. Come on.
Just stay there, Kuya.
Uh...
Name, please.
Chubi.
Chubi, okay, okay. Where are you seated?
- Oh, over there.
- Estong?
- Uh, we'll just serve them at your table.
- Okay, thank you.
Also, about the...
Can we talk?
May I take your order?
Can we please talk?
"Can we please talk?"
That's not on the menu, ma'am. Sorry.
I read the journal.
Everything written there,
about the exhibit...
and everything you've done for me.
Everything...
Everything I don't remember. I read it all.
Ma'am, there are customers waiting.
It's embarrassing for me to admit this...
but I think I owe you an apology.
Sorry.
I'm really sorry, Estong.
You didn't deserve what I did to you.
You didn't deserve
everything I said to you.
You didn't desereve to be used like that...
just so I could get close to Lorenz again.
I'm sorry.
Are you going to order?
Because if not, maybe you should leave.
I'm doing business here.
Alright.
I'll just be a customer for now.
How many coffees do I need to order
for you to forgive me?
Can you afford to buy all the coffee here?
Well, then, you can't buy my forgiveness.
Okay?
- One Ysabelle's Mocha—
- Sold out.
Fine, I'll have an
Americano instead.
Okay, just move over
to the side, thank you.
Side. Side, please.
One Americano.
Ma'am, your order, please!
Estong.
Iced Americano.
Okay.
Yes?
Thank you.
- Your order, please.
- Thank you.
Thank you! I'll just be over there.
Thank you.
Thank you, Estong.
Your order, please.
Estong, thank you!
Hmm, okay.
- Here's the menu.
- You're also having an Americano?
Two Americanos? Alright.
Thank you.
I'm done with number four, Kuya.
You're done...
Disgusting! After just being
done with number four.
I bet
you won't be able to resist Ate Belle.
Are you challenging me?
But it's true, isn't it?
Three days max, Kuya.
But then again...
maybe for you,
it's only three minutes.
Bro, can you just leave for a second?
Go get the orders ready for...
for Chubi, go ahead, go on.
Come on, there are quite a lot of them.
Go!
Uh, so two Americanos.
Do you want food with that?
I'd like to order again.
[Humming]
What is it this time?
One Ysabelle's Mocha Magic.
It's sold out, okay?
What do you mean, sold out?
But you just served that
drink to two other people.
What about her? You gave her
Ysabelle's Mocha Magic.
That was the last one.
How about a cappucino?
It's also sold out.
What kind of coffee shop
doesn't have coffee?
You've already ordered three.
So?
What if Lola Iska comes
out and scolds me again?
Mhm...
What?
You're still concerned.
I'm concerned about all of my customers.
I even suggested a salad to her.
Estong, I'm sorry, okay?
What do I need to do for you to forgive me?
Do you want me to be a dishwasher?
A barista? A server? What?
I'll even work part-time here.
Come on.
So you'll forgive me. I'm sorry, okay?
There are already a lot
of customers behind you.
Look, there's already a line.
- Order?
- Capuccino, sir.
There you go.
He's finally showing some
character development.
Oh,
the day's still young.
I know your brother.
Uh...
Belle, dear?
Yes?
Sorry,
we're closing now.
Oh...
I see. Okay.
- I'll also be heading out now.
- Alright.
Is it Estong?
Uh...looks like he's already resting.
He must be exhausted.
Ah...
It's okay.
I'll go ahead now.
Alright, dear.
- Okay. Take care now.
- Thank you.
Kuya,
Kuya.
don't you feel bad?
Just talk to her.
Kuya, I think she really regrets it.
She’s been here all day waiting for you.
That's her choice, bro.
I'm just worried
something might trigger her.
So what?
Now, it's my fault?
It's not like that, Kuya.
It's okay, Belle.
What is it now?
Nothing.
I just want to tell you that...
I'm proud of you.
You apologized to Estong...
you confronted Lorenz.
Good job.
I don't need your advice.
I don't need your help.
I don't need help from all of you!
Do you know why everything is such a mess?
Because of you.
Because of all of you and
everything you've done!
I only did what I thought was right
and what was best for all of us.
Well, no.
And it's none of your business.
I don't need you, because this is my life!
This is my life! Mine alone!
So from now on...
I'll handle things on my own.
Stay out of my business.
All of you!
Belle.
I can handle myself.
I don't need anyone.
No one will ever hurt me again.
- So what happened was, he saw Alora...
- Thank you!
when she left early
and even said goodbye.
We still got half a
kilo of orders, right?
Ah, that's why they weren't around.
- And guess where she went?
- Where?
Just around Divisoria.
She was looking for makeup that would make
her look as beautiful as you.
Hey,
woah...
Wow!
Dear, do you have a photoshoot?
Wow, sweetheart.
You look so beautiful today!
Ate Belle,
- how did your interview with Lorenz go?
- Oh, right!
Is it still happening?
When are they releasing it?
Oh, you might become famous.
Oh, not anymore.
It's not happening anymore,
and let's not talk about
people who are worthless.
I'll get going now.
Sweetheart, wait. Um...
Uh, have you talked to Estong already?
Not yet, Nang.
I also don't want to force myself on him.
I'll be going now.
Wait a minute.
Where are you going?
Want me to come with you?
Oh, no, Nong.
I just have something to
finish for my next commission.
I'll be going now.
Alright, take care, okay?
Do you have an order?
One large iced mocha.
One iced mocha.
Anything else?
That's all.
Okay.
Just bring it to my table.
Looks like you're the
one being avoided now.
I told you, Kuya.
Go on, sulk some more.
And you're rubbing it in.
What an idiot.
But Kuya...
she came back, okay?
Oh, right.
It's her routine.
Alright, Dad. Go start cooking.
Okay.
Why are you bossing me around?
May I take your order?
One of these?
- Adel...
- Drinks? Any drinks?
did you miss me again?
Give the phone to Kuya Estong.
Kuya,
it's Adel. She wants to talk to you.
- A latte, and this one.
- Latte. Yeah, okay.
What did he say?
Adel, what is it?
Uh, is Ate Belle there?
She's here.
Why? Did something happen?
Ninang Barbs is worried.
She seems different today.
She doesn't want to talk about Lorenz.
We're all worried
she might do something.
What's the tea?
You know, I was just thinking...
we should've all been
Team Estong from the start.
Well... how were we supposed to know
Lorenz was a red flag?
- Oh, yeah.
- I told you. We're Team Estong!
- That's how it should've been!
- What a shame!
You know...
what matters is that
Estong and Belle need to make up.
So we all need to come together
and help them reconcile.
They really just need to talk.
Well, Nang...
They're both being stubborn.
If only we could lock them
in a room together.
Wait. Hold on.
Hello?
Uh, hello?
Um, is this Bert? Estong's father?
Ah, yes. that's me.
I'm Barbs. Belle's mother.
Can we talk about the kids?
Uh, sure. Why, is there a problem?
Because we need to find a way
to keep the situation from getting worse.
Okay, I'll call you later
when I close the cafe.
And when the whole neighborhood
isn't listening in on you.
Here you go, thank you.
Oh, okay. Thank you!
Hello. Hello!
We don't know what to do
with Belle anymore.
Oh, I know.
It's the same with Estong.
I don't know what to do anymore either.
You know,
they're both so stubborn,
and so are their hearts.
Tell me about it.
Well...
we can't really blame them.
You know, I'm not asking
them to be in a relationship.
All I want is for things to
go back to how they were,
even just as friends.
I agree.
I'd rather they just stay friends than...
force it, right?
So...
what can we do?
Well...
we can start with the simplest thing.
Get them to talk things out.
Oh, everybody's already thought of that.
Do you think that can still
work with them?
I don't know, but...
it's better for us to try
than to do nothing.
Okay, but we need to
plan this carefully, okay?
Because if they find
out, I'm sure they'll bail.
Oh, you're right.
Alright, let's plan it out, okay?
Can you guys keep a secret
from your daughter? I know I can.
Is he going to take much longer, Nang?
And are you sure he really wants
to commission a painting?
Yes, yes, dear.
Just a little longer.
Uh...he just came from a meeting.
Let's just wait.
He’ll be here soon.
He's taking too long.
Sweetheart.
I'm sorry.
What's with the drama, Nang?
It's nothing.
Well... I was just thinking
that we haven't really gone out much
with your Nonong lately.
Sometimes I feel like I spend more time
with the rice than I do with you.
So it is drama.
Nang, that's okay.
And I know you're all doing
those things for me.
But, Nanang...
if you want, we could...
reduce my therapy sessions.
Why?
Nothing. Just to...
cut down on expenses.
Besides, I'm doing fine now.
Oh, no, dear.
Don't worry about the expenses.
As long as your Nonong
and I can, we'll help you.
And, dear,
there's nothing wrong with accepting help.
You don't have to handle
everything on your own.
You don't have to prove to yourself
that you can do it alone.
Not just from us.
From everyone who cares about you, too.
Oh, stop.
Nang, I don't want to talk about him.
I didn't mention a name.
But I already know what you mean.
Sweetheart, it's not just Estong.
Where the hell is Estong?
Where is he?
Estong!
Hurry up.
The deliveries are waiting.
Okay, game.
- Is this everything, Pops?
- Yeah, that's everything.
- Wow!
- Okay, go, go ahead.
That smells amazing.
Perfect timing.
- For what?
- No, uh...
What he meant was, it's perfect timing
because you've got a lot of deliveries.
- Come on, come on.
- Yeah, Kuya.
It'd be be embarrassing for the
customers, right? You should smell good.
You know what, let's do
the restaurant delivery first.
They said it's a rush order.
Okay, come on, come on.
It's a restaurant. Don't
they have coffee there?
Why does it have to be
a rush? What's the hurry?
No, they prefer our coffee
during the staff's break.
It's stronger, so it helps
them wake up more.
Wait a minute, I'll just use the restroom.
Wait, no, no, no.
Bro,
don't.
They asked us to hurry, remember?
They've been waiting for us.
You deliver it instead, bro.
I feel like it'll be quicker if you do it.
- Uh, no, no.
- He'll take care of it, Pops.
You two should just go together.
That way, you'll get there...
faster, right?
What's the.. what's the difference, Pops?
Something got in my eye.
Hey, bro, what's happening to you?
Nothing. I just got some
gunk stuck in my eye.
Oh.
- Oh, come on, just go.
- Come on, let's go.
- You need to go.
- Wait, hold on.
Pops, the supplier texted.
We need to pick up
the beans from them now.
It's urgent.
I'll take care of it. I'll go.
Then who's staying here?
I'll do it, Pops.
It's on the way, so we'll just
make a quick stop.
Then we'll head straight to the delivery.
But Kuya...
It's just that...
Bro, you talk too much.
Let's just go so we can finish this faster.
- I'll just warm up the car.
- Kuya...
Well, hurry up and
catch up! Belle is waiting.
Oh, yeah.
You already know, okay?
I just look like I've got something
in my eye, but you look retarded.
He's not yet here, Nang?
Should we just go home?
Guys, guys!
No, it's okay. He'll be here soon.
Um...his meeting ran late.
We've been waiting here for a while now.
Yes, sweetheart. Just a little while.
Let's just wait for him, okay?
- Guys! That's her.
- Are you sure?
Just a moment. I'll just call your Nonong.
She's the one in the video.
I told you! Look.
Look at the face!
That's her, right?
[laughing]
She's the crazy girl.
Hello.
Hello?
- Where is he?
- He's on the way.
What's taking him so long?
Oh, he still had a lot of stops to make.
I even had Jayden go with him
to keep things moving.
She's getting impatient.
Tell him to go here already, okay?
Hey, bro. Let's go.
Let's load these up.
I'll take that, Kuya.
That's her, she's the insane girl.
She's the one going viral.
[laughing]
Hey, that's her, right?
[crowd laughing]
Nang?
Yeah?
Oh, sweetheart! You know what?
I'm starving.
Why don't we order something inside again?
Nang, do I have something on my face?
No, you don't.
Then why are they staring at me?
That might be contagious!
We might get infected.
It's you!
What? Me?
The crazy one.
Hey! Watch your mouth!
You're the one who went viral!
- Here, look!
- What are you talking about?
So you’re a prick, huh?
What the hell are you saying?!
- You wanna fight?!
- Bro, stop filming.
It's terrifying.
It's chilling...
Our team captured footage of
a woman who allegedly has
"split personality."
But does she really have split
personality disorder?
Or is this woman just
being overly dramatic?
Or could she actually be
losing her mind?
The strange, chilling, and terrifying
story of this young woman…
only here at KKK!
Belle, I thought Lorenz
wasn’t going to release that.
It's her!
It's really her! She's
the crazy girl! It's her!
Hey!
What's your problem?
What are you all saying?!
Can you all stop? Come on!
What the hell?
Put your phones away! Come on!
- Come on! Stop it!
- Can you show us the old woman, ma'am?
Crazy girl!
Hey! Knock it off!
Stop that!
Come on! I said—
Stop it! Leave me alone! Leave me alone!
Belle!
- Belle!
- Ma'am! Ma'am!
- I'm gonna go to Lorenz!
- Stop it! Delete that!
Delete that, okay? Delete
what's on your phones.
Stop it!
- So, I'll just transfer it to you, and—
- Kuya!
Kuya, come here.
Look at this.
What is it?
Kuya...
it's Ate Belle and Tita.
Belle?
Hello? Estong?
Tita, how are you guys doing?
Estong, help me!
I don't know where Belle went.
The video is out. It's already gone viral.
People are making fun of her.
Uh, okay, Tita.
I'll help you. I'll also look for Belle.
Okay, okay. Hey! Stop it! Leave me alone!
Kuya,
Kuya...
I'll take it from here.
I'll call Adel for the tracker,
then I'll send you Ate
Belle's location, okay?
Alright.
- Bro, you got it from here, okay?
- Yes, Kuya.
I'll send it to you, okay?
Belle.
Hello, Adel!
Congratulations, Bee!
Our show is successful.
Hey, bro, congrats!
- Thank you, thank you, thank you.
- Your ratings are pretty high, huh?
How...
How dare you!
How could you do that to me?!
It's all part of the job.
I'm going to sue you.
I'll take you to court.
What I did was legal, Belle.
What?
You thought you could trick me?
What do you mean, legal?
You had no right to make decisions for me!
I do.
You signed an agreement
before I filmed you, remember?
I didn't sign it.
I didn't sign anything.
I have a copy with your signature.
Finally! It's my stardom era.
I'll get so famous here!
Whoever signed it, it wasn't me.
No matter which of your
personalities signed it,
it was still you.
You are one person.
So everything's legal.
I didn't do anything wrong.
It's not my fault.
You...
You shameless prick! You bastard!
- Stop it.
- How could you do this to me!
I can't control them.
So many people are making
fun of me because of you!
I can't control how people would react!
How could you do this to—
Belle?
Belle, are you okay?
Belle? Belle, are you okay?
What's your problem?!
Don't touch me!
You know? You're such a user.
I shouldn't have trusted you
if I'd known you'd do this to us!
You know what?
You're bad.
Uh, no, no. Shhh.
You're bad! You're bad! You hurt us!
You hurt Yeye! You hurt me! You're bad!
People like you have a place in hell.
I've been wanting to do
this to you for a long time.
What? Got something to say?! Speak up!
You're really losing your mind!
Is that how your parents raised you?
Huh?
That's not good manners!
What you did was wrong!
What you did was terrible!
No, no...
We didn't deserve what you did to us.
You didn't deserve our trust.
- Ah! I'm not done with you yet! Not yet!
- Don't, don't! Please, no more!
- You got something to say? What, nothing?!
- No, no, no...
- No, no, no? "No" your face! Get up!
- No, please, please. That's enough.
No more.
What, can't you get up?!
Oh...is that so?!
Get up!
Get up. Come on, get up!
Please, please. No more, no more!
- No more?!
- So get up. Get up. Huh?!
- Please, stop.
You're not gonna say
anything? What? What?!
Please, please, stop!
- You shameless prick!
- Belle!
- Please, stop. Please.
- Belle! Belle! That's enough!
I'm not yet done with you!
Enough. That's enough.
You okay?
Es...Estong, it's me...
Ysa.
Don't you worry.
I'm here now,
okay?
Are you okay?
Let's go?
You freaks! Freaks!
Ysa, don't worry, okay?
We'll have the video taken down.
We'll find a way to press
charges against them.
Ysa?
Uh...Belle?
Belle?
You can try hitting him in
the chest like this.
Then, hit him like this.
Just like that. It looks easy, right?
It's really easy.
Pow, pow, pow. Then...
Hey! Don't just feed me whatever this is.
Hey, look. The TV's on.
Hello, Estong?
Yes, Tita Barbs?
Estong, where are you guys?
Uh, we're on our way, Tita.
We're coming.
Okay, we'll wait for you.
Alright.
Where are we going?
We're going to see Dr. Wanda.
He's taking us to the hospital.
I'm sure
this is a different level of intervention
to get us better.
No.
I don't want to.
Belle,
don't be scared.
We'll be with you.
I don't need any of you!
Calm down, my child.
Calm down.
I am not your child
and you are not my grandmother,
so leave me alone!
Belle...
Ysa! Come on, be quiet!
Belle?
Belle, what's happening?
I don't want to go to the hospital.
Stop the car!
Belle, please.
This is for you, okay?
We need to do this.
Just trust us.
- I don't want to do this.
- Be—Belle, calm down, please.
Estong, come on!
Belle, don't!
Ysa, stop!
Estong, stop this!
Estong, stop the car, come on!
Belle!
Estong's gonna get hurt!
Can you all please be quiet?!
OMG! You might crash the car, Belle!
Dear!
Please!
I don't need any of you! Leave me alone!
Leave me alone!
Belle? Belle, just calm down.
Estong!
- Stop the car, Estong! Stop the car!
- Belle, Belle!
Belle! What you're doing is dangerous!
I'm scared!
- Estong, come on! I said stop the car!
- Belle!
That's enough!
So please stop the car, come on!
I'll try to do something!
Estong.
Ysa?
Estong, we're trying to stop Belle.
Uh, what should I do?
- I can't! I can't!
- What? What?
Estong, stop it!
Come on, listen to me!
Bogart! Your turn,
she might listen to you!
Okay.
Bro!
- Just hang on!
- I'm hanging on, bro!
Bro, calm down! Bro!
Bro?
She doesn't want to!
Stop it, what is wrong
with you?! Listen to me!
- Ah, Belle!
- I don't want to go there!
Cacai! You should... you, uh... you...
it's your turn!
OMG! Jestoni,
I'm getting so dizzy!
Cacai, we're almost
there. We're getting there.
My gosh!
My head!
Oh my God, I can't do this!
Estong, come on! Stop the car!
- Baby Girl, take over!
- No, oh my.
Best friend!
Yeye is scared!
Yeye's scared!
I know, Yeye.
I'm sorry, best friend.
Let's play later, okay?
Stop the car!
I can't!
Stop!
That's enough. Stop the car. Stop!
- Kuya Tristan! You do it!
- Yeah, you.
Bro, can you still do it?
Yeah, Tristan.
I can do it.
- What? Nothing?
- Nothing.
Estong, stop the car. I said stop it!
Enough! That's enough!
Lola, maybe you can give it a try.
Try it, Lola. Maybe
she'll listen to the elderly.
My child...
Lola?
Lola, wake up.
This is dangerous...
This is dangerous, Lola.
Lola?
Lola? Lola! Lola?
- Oh my God!
- Lola? Lola! Lola!
Sorry, I fell asleep.
Damn it!
Lola!
What now?!
- Estong, just stop it, okay?
- Belle!
Belle.
Belle!
Estong?
Hey! Estong!
Estong!
Estong! Estong, no! Estong!
Mommy?
Daddy?
Mommy! Daddy!
Estong!
Estong, Estong, Estong? Estong!
Estong...
I'm just trying to be
normal, but no...
I'm cursed!
- We're all cursed!
- Sweetheart, no.
That's enough, sweetheart.
No, that's not true.
It seems like the stress was
too much for her body.
But it’s also possible for
a personality to show up more often,
or maybe...
someone we haven't met
yet might come out.
Doc, are there others?
It's possible.
Belle, what did you do?!
This is what you all wanted, right?
For all of us to be together?
Fine, then. I’ll give you exactly that!
- We can't find Belle!
- Did you see her?
You know, we haven’t been
able to contact her all day.
Belle?
Belle!
Who are you?
A new alter?